Register of the Center for the Study of Popular Culture Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- National Association of Scholars seventh national conference, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1997 December 12-14. (Folder 45: 19)
  Invitation to participate in panel discussion and miscellany
- Speech, Center of the American Experience, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1998 January 27. (Folder 45: 20)
  Typescript speech, letters, itinerary, receipts, and schedule
- Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, Illinois, 1998 January 28. (Folder 45: 21)
  Includes letter of invitation to deliver a lecture and related materials
- Educational Policy Conference, Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1998 January 29-30. (Folder 45: 22-23)
  Letters, including one inviting David Horowitz to speak, receipt, and miscellany
- Brady Foundation board meeting, San Francisco, California, 1998 February 5. (Folder 45: 24)
  Letters
- Council for National Policy, Phoenix, Arizona, 1998 February 7. (Folder 45: 25)
  Letters and schedule
- Northwest Business Club, Bellingham, Washington, 1998 February 11. (Folder 45: 26)
  Letters, fact sheet, and printed matter
- Buck and Ballot Brigade Lincoln day dinner, Bookerson Group, Glendale, California, 1998 February 19. (Folder 45: 27)
  Letters and miscellany
- Indianapolis Chamber of Commerce, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1998 March 4. (Folder 45: 28)
  Invitation to be a featured speaker, itinerary, receipt, and related materials
- "The Big Picture: Liberty or Global Governance," Eagle Forum of California annual conference, Santa Barbara, California, 1998 March 20. (Folder 45: 29)
  Announcement
- Forum on the republican future, sponsored by the Harris County Republican Party, Houston, Texas, 1998 March 25-28. (Folder 45: 30)
  Itinerary, letters, printed matter, and related materials
- Reviews of Radical Son by David Horowitz, 1997 March – April. (Box-folder 46: 1)
  Includes a letter announcing a search for the position of president of Buckeye Institute, Ohio, and printed matter
- Penn State Speech Forum, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, 1997 March 5. (Folder 46: 2)
  Includes announcement and receipt
- "Lecture on Radical Son: From Sixties Radical to Nineties Conservative," Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1997 March 7. (Folder 46: 3)
  Includes review of David Horowitz, Radical Son
- Hungry Mind Bookstore, St. Paul, Minnesota--Event to read from Radical Son by David Horowitz, 1997 March 9. (Folder 46: 4)
  Includes related materials
- The Hartland Institute, Palatine, Illinois, 1997 March 18. (Folder 46: 5)
  Luncheon for promotion of Radical Son. Includes related materials
- Hudson Institute, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1997 March 17. (Folder 46: 6)
  Papers relating to the planning of David Horowitz's lecture on Radical Son
- Bel Air Republican Women Federated, Los Angeles, California, 1997 March 24. (Folder 46: 7)
  Thank you letter for speech
- Harris County Republican Party, Houston, Texas, 1997 April 1. (Folder 46: 8)
- Letters and miscellaneous materials relating to David Horowitz's speech and book signing event
- University of Texas, Austin, Texas, 1997 April 2. (Folder 46: 9)
  Materials relating to David Horowitz's speaking engagement
- The University of Mississippi, Mississippi, 1997 April 9. (Folder 46: 10)
  Includes itinerary and letters relating to David Horowitz's visit
- Freedom conference, Salisbury State University College, Salisbury, Maryland, 1997 April 12. (Folder 46: 11)
  Speaking agenda and related materials
- Allegheny Institute, Pittsburgh, Philadelphia, 1997 April 17. (Folder 46: 12)
  Letters relating to David Horowitz's visit and miscellany
- Malibu Women's Club, Malibu, California, 1997 April 21. (Folder 46: 13)
- Invitation to visit Washington University, Pullman, Washington, 1997 April 24. (Folder 46: 14-15)
  Itinerary, receipts, and miscellany
- Youth Leadership Institute, 1997 April 26. (Folder 46: 16)
  Speaking engagement fact sheet
- University of Washington, Seattle, Washington, 1997 April 25. (Folder 46: 17)
  Itinerary and receipts
- Century City Rotary Club, Los Angeles, California, 1997 April 30. (Folder 46: 18)
  Letters confirming speaking engagement and luncheon
- San Diego Republican Women, San Diego Republican Party, 1997 May 15. (Folder 46: 19)
  Receipts, schedule, and other related materials
- Palos Verdes Peninsula Republican Women Federated, Palos Verdes Peninsula, California, 1997 May 27. (Folder 46: 20)
  Includes letter of invitation to speak, clippings, and printed matter
- A Celebration of Freedom: 10th anniversary gala honoring Oliver North, Washington, D.C., 1997 July 8. (Folder 46: 21)
  Fact sheet
- Trip to Houston, Texas, 1997 June. (Folder 46: 22)
  Itinerary and schedule
- Arlen Specter DreamWorks reception, Los Angeles, California, 1997 June 9. (Folder 46: 23)
  Includes clipping about Arlen Specter and related materials
- Trip to Washington, D.C., 1997 July (Folder 46: 24)
- Team 100 summer national meeting, National Republican Senatorial Committee, California, 1997 July 10-11. (Folder 46: 25)
  Letters of invitation, schedule, and related materials
- Trip to San Francisco, California, 1997 July 17. (Folder 46: 26)
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1994-1996 (Box 47)
  and 1 compact disc recording TV interviews about education and politics
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1994-2000 (Box 48)
  recording talks about education, politics, and land rights; a debate about V-chip; and a conversation with Jim Lehrer
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1994-2001. (Box 49)
  Subjects include swing of the movie industry to the right, film festival, Republican Party's political agenda, appearance of David Horowitz on CNN, and miscellany
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1994-1995 (Box 50)
  relating to the role of ideology in American politics, California's controversial proposition 187, issues of immigration, and activities of religious organizations
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1994 and undated (Box 51)
  relating to National Review Institute, Los Angeles, California. Also records commercials by Oliver North
- 12 VHS videocassettes, 1995-2002. (Box 52)
  Relate to America's national security
- 14 VHS videocassettes, 2001-2002. (Box 53)
  Primarily relate to national security. Also records David Horowitz on CNN and C-Span programs
- Wednesday Morning Club (Box 54)
  - Steering committee meeting, 1996 (Folder 54: 1)
  - Banquet at Hotel Nikko. (Folder 54: 2-3)
    Includes 1 photographic print depicting Christopher Cox and information packet about Hotel Nikko, 1997
  - Steering committee dinner, 1996 (Folder 54: 4)
  - Ken Khachigian and Bill Carrick. (Folder 54: 5)
    Includes 2 contact sheets and 2 photographic prints depicting unidentified individuals, 1996
  - William Schneider, 1996 (Folder 54: 6)
  - Paul Maslin and Frank Luntz, 1996. (Folder 54: 7)
    Includes 1 compact sound cassette
  - Forum series, 1991-1996 (Folder 54: 8)
- 1996 Golfing for Kids--Tee gift packages (Folder 54: 9)
  Brochure, receipt, printed matter, and miscellany
- American Cinema Foundation, 1995. (Folder 54: 10)
- PSA for CEO America, 1994-1996. (Folder 54: 11)
  Includes materials relating to Golfing for Kids
- Wednesday Morning Club (Box 55)
  - Robert Bork, 1996 (Folder 55: 1)
  - Newt Gingrich, 1996 (Folder 55: 2)
- Tony Snow, 1996. (Folder 55: 3)
  Includes 1 photographic print depicting Tony Snow
- President's golf challenge--Car sponsorships, 1996 (Folder 55: 4)
- Fred Thompson's visit to Los Angeles, California, 1996 (Folder 55: 5)
- Best Friends, 1996. (Folder 55: 6)
  Miscellaneous information
- Children's Educational Opportunity (CEO)--Charter School Initiative, 1996. (Folder 55: 7)
  Printed matter
- Planet Hollywood event, 1996 August. (Folder 55: 8)
- Photographers--2 hours of photo coverage of the Wednesday Morning Club, 1996 (Folder 55: 9)
- Advertisers--Program and ticket sales, 1996 (Folder 55: 10)
- Second annual Images of Ourselves conference sponsored by the Center for the Study of Popular Culture and Wednesday Morning Club, Walt Disney Studios, California, 1997 March 22. (Folder 55: 11)
  Letters to participants
- List of top 50 Silicon Valley sponsors, 1997 January (Folder 55: 12)
- Company ideas--List of initial contacts, 1997 January (Folder 55: 13)
- Gift bag items, 1997 March (Folder 55: 14)
- Images of Ourselves conference, 1997. (Folder 55: 15)
  Brochures, fliers, list of panel participants, registration form, and related materials
- "Changing Environments: Politics, Technology, Culture," Images of Ourselves Conference, Burbank, California (Box 56)
  - Invitations, 1997 (Folder 56: 1)
  - Variety, 1996 (Folder 56: 2)
  - Decorations/centerpieces, undated (Folder 56: 3)
  - Edgar Scherick's testimonials, 1997 (Folder 56: 4)
  - Public relations, 1997 (Folder 56: 5)
  - Bobby Duron--Photographer, undated (Folder 56: 6)
  - Invoices and budget, 1994-1997 (Folder 56: 7-9)
  - Logistics, 1997 (Folder 56: 10)
  - Interactive/news media, 1996-1997 (Folder 56: 11)
  - Images locale, 1997 (Folder 56: 12)
  - Conference planning, 1994-1996 (Folder 56: 13)
  - Fundraising packet, 1996 (Folder 56: 14)
  - Sheraton Universal, 1996 (Folder 56: 15)
  - Disney and volunteers, 1996-1997 (Folder 56: 16-17)
  - Press, undated (Folder 56: 18)
  - E-Online, undated (Folder 56: 19)
  - Images information, 1997 (Folder 56: 20)
  - Fliers, 1997 (Folder 56: 21)
  - Panel topics, 1997 (Folder 56: 22)
  - Images related press clips, 1997 (Folder 56: 23)
  - Program, 1997 (Folder 56: 24)
  - Images--Sponsors, 1995-1996 (Folder 56: 25)
  - Richard J. Riordan's letter, 1997 (Folder 56: 26)
  - Dialogue between Washington and Hollywood, 1996 February 24
- Radical Son by David Horowitz, 1997-2002. (Box-folder 57: 1)
- Sex/military, 1997 May 9. (Folder 57: 2)
  Clippings
- "Clinton Proves GOP Right on Welfare," by David Horowitz, San Francisco Chronicle, 1996 August 9 (Folder 57: 3)
- 1996 Election--Clippings (Folder 57: 4)
- K. L. Billingsley--Articles, 1996-1997. (Folder 57: 5-6)
- E-Net--Printed matter, 1996 (Folder 57: 7)
- A. T. Kearney--Education, 1996. (Folder 57: 8)
  Articles
- Education
  - Class size, 1996. (Folder 57: 9)
  - Golfing for Kids, 1996. (Folder 57: 10)
    Articles and related printed matter
  - Proposition--Bond campaign, 1997. (Folder 57: 11)
  - Report card ads and reprints, 1995 (Folder 57: 12)
  - School performance, 1994-1996 (Folder 57: 13)
  - School reform, 1996 (Folder 57: 14)
  - Union, 1996 (Folder 57: 15)
  - Vouchers/choice, 1996 (Folder 57: 16)
  - Miscellany (Folder 57: 17)
- Fathers and families, 1996-1997 (Folder 57: 18)
- Hollywood--Children's TV and Conservatism, 1995-1997 (Folder 57: 19-20)
- Hollywood--Articles by and about David Horowitz, clippings, and photocopies. (Box 58)
  Includes articles by others
  - Images II, 1997 (Folder 58: 1)
  - Insight--Horowitz/Collier, 1992 (Folder 58: 2)
  - Politically correct, 1994-1996 (Folder 58: 3)
  - Race, 1993-1996 (Folder 58: 4)
  - V-Chip media content, 1995-1996 (Folder 58: 5-7)
  - Wednesday Morning Club (WMC) events, 1994-1997 (Folder 58: 8-9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Folder 58: 10)
- David Horowitz
  - "Cop Bashing,", 1996 (Folder 58: 11)
  - Public Broadcasting Service (PBS), 1994 (Folder 58: 12)
  - Tom Hayden, 1997 (Folder 58: 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968 and; 1994-1997 (Folder 58: 14)
  - 1996 election (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Affirmative action, 1997 (Folder 59: 2)
  - Politically correct, 1994 (Folder 59: 3)
  - Race, 1994-1997 (Folder 59: 4)
  - Miscellaneous
    - American Cinema Foundation, 1995-1996 (Folder 59: 5)
    - Budget, 1997 (Folder 59: 6)
    - Center, 1995-1997 (Folder 59: 7)
    - Center split, 1995 (Folder 59: 8)
    - Conservatism, 1993 (Folder 59: 9)
    - Race/military, 1997 (Folder 59: 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Folder 59: 11)
- News releases, 1995-1997 (Folder 59: 12-13)
- Panthers, 1993-1995 (Folder 59: 14)
- Panthers, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 60: 1)
- Public media, 1994 (Folder 60: 2-5)
- David Horowitz--Bio/overview, convention/media, and conservatism, 1992-1997 (Folder 60: 6-8)
- Josephson, Larry Bridges--Letters, memoranda, contact list, and registration form, 1997 (Box-folder 61: 1)
- "Images of Ourselves: A Dialogue between Washington and Hollywood"
  - Typescript copies, 1996 February 24
  - Brochures, undated
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1996-1997
  - Biographical information on others, 1997
  - Variety's on Production, 1997 March
  - Articles, 1997
  - Miscellany, 1997
- Palmer R. Chitester Fund, 1999. (Box-folder 62: 1)
  Letter to David Horowitz
- "Nichols Case"--Interviews of listeners, final report, and memoranda, 1999 (Folder 62: 2-3)
- "Images of Ourselves" conference, Hollywood, California, 1996 February 24. (Folder 62: 4-5)
  Includes financial statements, itineraries, letters, memoranda, phone list, and other related materials, 1995-1997
- Information relating to the Golfing for Kids event, Carlsbad, California, 1996 August 11-12
- Newspaper and miscellany, 1997
- Hispanic vote, 1997. (Box-folder 63: 1)
  Includes letters, photocopy of articles, and report
- Hertz Rent-a-Car, 1999. (Folder 63: 2)
  Agreement, statement of account, and related materials
- "Images of Ourselves: A Dialogue between Washington and Hollywood,", 1996 February
- Public media, 1995. (Box-folder 64: 1-2)
  Clippings (photocopies) about Public Broadcasting Service (PBS)
- Photocopy of an article by Christopher Rapp, 1997 (Folder 64: 3)
- Kevin Teasley--Biographical information, undated (Folder 64: 4)
- Newspaper clippings and photocopies of articles about Angela Davis, 1995 (Folder 64: 5)
- Clippings and articles about Hollywood, 1994-1996 (Folder 64: 6)
- Henry Kissinger and Richard Nixon--Clippings, 1995-1996 (Folder 64: 7)
- Miscellany--Clippings and articles, 1995-1996 (Folder 64: 8)
  including one by David Horowitz
- Unbound copy of "Destructive Generation,", undated
- NYE County, Nevada (Box 65)
  - Old newspaper clips, 1995 (Folder 65: 1-2)
  - Colleges, 1995 (Folder 65: 3)
  - Panthers, 1994-1995 (Folder 65: 4)
  - Public Broadcasting Service (PBS), 1995 (Folder 65: 5-6)
  - Rose Kennedy, 1995 (Folder 65: 7)
- Photocopies of articles by others, 1994-1995
- Race--Old newspaper clips, 1995 (Box-folder 66: 1)
- Dark Ages--"Reactionary Romp," article by David Van Biema, Time, 1996 (Folder 66: 2)
- Politics, 1996. (Folder 66: 3)
  Photocopies of articles about politics in various newspapers
- Golfing for Kids, 1996. (Folder 66: 4)
  Articles and related information
- E Pluribus Unum awards, 1995-1995. (Folder 66: 5-6)
- Miscellany, 1997-2002.
  Congratulatory letters to David Horowitz and certificate from the Commonwealth Club of California
- Clippings, 1994-1995
- "Summer Adventure Abroad"--Collage, undated
- "Images of Ourselves: A Dialogue between Washington and Hollywood,", 1996 February 24 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  --HC book proposal, reported by Anita Noble
- Call to Action: Governor Pete Wilson's conference for women, Long Beach, California, 1996 November 14. (Folder 67: 2)
- Il Postino--Heterodoxy, 1996. (Folder 67: 3)
  Form letters from David Horowitz and clippings
- "We the People: Public Lands/States' Rights," conference, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1995 January 20-21. (Folder 67: 4)
- Center for the Study of Popular Culture--Benefactors' reception, Los Angeles, California, 1996 February 23. (Folder 67: 5)
  Includes letters, invoices, lists, and related materials
- Individual Rights Foundation--Affiliates letters, 1995 September – October. (Folder 67: 6-7)
  Includes letters and lists
- Investigative Journalism Project, 1995. (Folder 67: 8)
  Letters and lists
- "Teach In" on affirmative action, University of California, Los Angeles, 1995 May 4. (Folder 67: 9)
  Lists of names and donations
- Center proposal--WL, 1995. (Folder 67: 10)
- Individual Rights Foundation proposal--WL, 1995. (Folder 67: 11)
- "Who's Ruining Our Schools?" CTI brochure, 1995. (Folder 67: 12)
  Letters and list of names
- Bill Huston, 1995. (Folder 67: 13)
  Letter and list of names
- Jobtrak: College Job Listing Service, 1994-1996. (Folder 67: 14-15)
- Images conference. (Box 68)
  Includes clippings, letters, invoice, lists of audios and videos, proposal, and miscellany
  - Video, 1996 (Folder 68: 1)
  - Advertising and invitations, 1995-1996 (Folder 68: 2)
  - Information and schedule, 1996 (Folder 68: 3)
  - Miscellany, 1996 (Folder 68: 4)
  - Paramount Pictures, 1996 (Folder 68: 5)
  - Registration, 1996 (Folder 68: 6)
  - Press clips, 1996 (Folder 68: 7)
  - Speakers
    - Al-L, 1996 (Folder 68: 8)
    - M-Z, 1996 (Folder 68: 9)
- Banquet in honor of Ward Connerly, Century City, California, 1995 May 4. (Folder 68: 10-12)
  Lists of attendees, contributions, letters including thank you letters to members of the host committee, and related information
- Ward Connerly banquet (Box 69)
  - List of invitees, undated (Folder 69: 1)
  - Program, 1995 (Folder 69: 2)
- "We the People: Public Lands/States Rights"--Individual Rights Foundation conference, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1995 January 20-21. (Folder 69: 3-7)
  Includes invitations, program, registration, and related information
- 15 photographic contact sheets, including 12 undated, and 3 from Tanzier, 1994 February 28 (Box-folder 70: 1)
- John Kasich--3 photographic contact sheets, 1997 April 9 (Folder 70: 2)
- Richard Gephardt, 1998 March 19. (Folder 70: 3)
  Letter of invitation from David Horowitz
- Dan Lungren, 1997-1998. (Folder 70: 4)
  Includes biographical information, letters, 1 photographic print depicting Dan Lungren, and miscellany
- Wednesday Morning Club
  - Letters relating to packets sent, 1997-1998 (Folder 70: 5-6)
  - Letters of expiration of membership, 1997-1998 (Folder 70: 7-8)
  - Charitable contribution receipts, 1998 (Folder 70: 9)
  - New members, 1997 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Correspondence sent and received, 1997 (Folder 70: 11-12)
  - Membership renewals, 1998 (Folder 70: 13)
  - Memoranda, 1997 (Folder 70: 14)
  - Newsletters, 1998 (Folder 70: 15)
- Chuck Fries Productions, Inc., 1997. (Box-folder 71: 1)
  Includes a letter to David Horowitz, biographical note, and lists of series and mini-series produced
- Biographies, 1997, of members of House of Representatives, United States Congress, including Frank D. Riggs, James E. Rogan, Rick Santorum, and J. C. Watts, Jr. (Folder 71: 2)
  Also includes mission statements from Renewal Alliance
- The Caucus for producers, writers, and directors, 1995. (Folder 71: 3)
  Memoranda
- Congressman Peter T. King, 1995-1996. (Folder 71: 4)
  Clippings and biographical note
- Wednesday Morning Club
  - Hollywood host for the governor, 1995 December 7. (Folder 71: 5)
  - Dick Armey, 1996. (Folder 71: 6)
    Includes announcement, clippings, and miscellany
  - Khachigian/Carrick, 1996. (Folder 71: 7)
    Receipts
  - Ron Brownstein, 1996. (Folder 71: 8)
  - Robert Bork, 1996 February 28. (Folder 71: 9)
    Letter from Kelly Novak from the Center to Jennifer Caterini
  - Frank Gaffney, 1996. (Folder 71: 10)
    Includes conversation, clippings, letters, lists, and related materials
  - John Kasich, 1996. (Folder 71: 11)
    Attendance list, clippings, letters, receipts, and miscellany
  - Billy Tauzin, 1997. (Folder 71: 12)
    Agenda, clippings, letters, and miscellany
  - J. C. Watts Jr. event, 1997. (Folder 71: 13)
    Budget forecast, list of attendees and reservation, memoranda, and program
  - Byron Dorgan, 1997. (Folder 71: 14)
  - Sam Brownback, 1997. (Folder 71: 15)
    Letters, list of attendees and invoices, memoranda, and receipts
  - Newt Gingrich event, 1998. (Box-folder 72: 1-2)
    Miscellaneous materials
  - Henry Hyde, 1998. (Folder 72: 3)
    Announcement, clippings, and report. Includes 28 photographic prints depicting David Horowitz, Thomas P. O'Neil, and some unidentified individuals, undated
- Keepers of Flame honoring POWs in Vietnam, 1997-1998. (Folder 72: 4)
  Clippings, notes, letters, and miscellany
- Rodney King incident, 1999. (Folder 72: 5)
- Application for temporary seller's permit, 1999 (Folder 72: 6)
- Nonexclusive wholesale consignment agreement with Partners/West, 1998-1999. (Folder 72: 7)
- Sex, Lies & Vast Conspiracies
  - Correspondence with different publishers for review, 1998 (Folder 72: 8)
  - Public relations information, 1998. (Folder 72: 9)
  - Sale invoices, 1998 (Folder 72: 10)
- Stokely Carmichael--Obituary by David Horowitz, 1998 (Folder 72: 11)
- Wednesday Morning Club, 1996-1999. (Folder 72: 12)
- Governor George W. Bush, 1998. (Folder 72: 13)
- Debates--California, 1998 fall. (Folder 72: 14)
  Letters sent to candidates for office in California, including Barbara Boxer, Gray Davis, Matt Fong, Dan Lungren, and others, inviting them to participate in luncheon debates hosted by the Wednesday Morning Club
- David Drier--Press release about a luncheon meeting hosted by Wednesday Morning Club, 1999 (Folder 72: 15)
- Matt Drudge--, 1998. (Folder 72: 16)
- Matt Fong, 1998. (Folder 72: 17)
  Press release regarding a luncheon meeting
- Bill Frist, 1998. (Folder 72: 18)
- Dore Gold, 1998. (Folder 72: 19)
  Clippings and related materials
- Orrin Hatch, 1998. (Folder 72: 20)
  Clippings, press release, and miscellany
- Arianna Huffington, 1998. (Folder 72: 21)
  Press release and miscellany
- John Kasich, 1999. (Folder 72: 22)
  Clippings and press release
- Bob Kerry, 1998. (Folder 72: 23)
  Letter from David Horowitz
- Bill Kristol, 1999. (Folder 72: 24)
- Chris Matthews, 1999. (Folder 72: 25)
- Leoluca Orlando, 1999. (Folder 72: 26)
  Biography, press release, and miscellany
- Leon Panetta, 1999. (Folder 72: 27)
  Biography and press releases
- John Stossel, 1998. (Folder 72: 28)
  Announcement, biography, and related materials
- "Why I Am Not a Liberal?" Washington Times, 1997. (Folder 72: 29)
  Includes related material
- George Will, 1998. (Folder 72: 30)
  Letter of invitation and related materials
- Pete Wilson, 1998. (Folder 72: 31)
  Press release
- Press, 1997. (Box-folder 73: 1)
  Biographies of members of Congress, press and address list, and press release
- School on Wheels, 1998. (Folder 73: 2)
- Miscellany, 1998. (Folder 73: 3)
  Includes biographies, clippings, and press release
- PR Newswire, undated. (Folder 73: 4)
  Press release distribution information
- Wednesday Morning Club--Press, 1996-1997. (Folder 73: 5)
  Clippings and press advisory
- Media lists, 1996-1997 (Folder 73: 6)
- Clippings, 1995-1997 (Folder 73: 7-8)
- Press, 1997. (Folder 73: 9-10)
  List of invitees to David Horowitz's book-signing ceremony at Wednesday Morning Club
- V-Chip, 1996. (Folder 73: 11)
  Biography of David Horowitz and clippings
- St. Louis, Missouri, 1998. (Folder 73: 12)
  Memorandum relating to David Horowitz's radio appearance
- Xpedite Systems, undated. (Folder 73: 13-14)
  Instructions
- Weekend press reports, 1998-1999. (Folder 73: 15)
- Miscellany, 2000. (Folder 73: 16)
  Letters to David Horowitz, cartoons, and drawings
- Channel City Club, 2000. (Folder 73: 17)
  Letter from Judith Hill
- Alaskan Republican Party, 2000. (Folder 73: 18)
  Itinerary, memoranda, and notes
- CATO Institute--Conference on "The Rule of Law in the Wake of Clinton,", 2000 July 12. (Folder 73: 19)
  Brochures, clippings, letters, memorandum, and program
- Thank you letters, 2000 (Folder 73: 20)
- Tom DeLay event, 2001. (Folder 73: 21)
  Includes letters of invitation, list of newspapers, and program
- Advertisements, 2001. (Folder 73: 22-23)
  Includes materials relating to advertising rates and policy
- SlapHillary.com, 2000. (Folder 73: 24)
  Advertisement and correspondence with William Blinn
- Jews, 1996-1999. (Folder 73: 25)
  Clippings, journals, newsletters, and notes
- Stationery, undated (Box-folder 74: 1)
- Sheila Kuehl, 1994-1996. (Folder 74: 2)
  Clippings and memoranda
- Diane Watson, 1984-1995. (Folder 74: 3)
- "The Honor and Duty of Fatherhood," 3rd annual fathers' conference, Anaheim, California, 1997 June 18-20. (Folder 74: 4)